# Wingo Chan Chi Chung

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### Contact

- wingowingo3210@gmail.com
- +852 5413 2525
- github.com/9www

### **Skills**

React, Nextjs, JavaScript, Vue, HTML/CSS, Unity C#, Spark Ar, PHP, Mysql, Adobe illustrator, Adobe Photoshop

# **Side Projects**

- Future Dashboard React.JS, API
- Personal website Next.JS
- 2d Game Pixel art gun game Unity C#
- 3d Game Puzzle game Unity C#

#### **About**

Hello, I'm Wingo, I born in design and multimedia field. I studied creative coding and game field in university periods. Also, I joined "Software Art studio" coding course in final year, which course have frontend knowledges. It is attract me and I want to understanding frontend knowledges and develop more frontend projects. Now I am a frontend developer.

# **Work Experience**

Cheil PengTai

Dec 2021 - Present

#### **Frontend Developer**

- Develop and maintain website Vue, CSS, API
- Maintain and develop website React, CSS and API
- Develop EDM HTML/ CSS

**Kontec Creative** 

Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

#### **Junior Software Engineer**

- Developed and web design responsive React, bootstrap and SCSS
- Enhanced website SEO rank and re-branding website Nextjs, SCSS and bootstrap
- Full stack development and design on the P&L form Vue, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, API and OctoberCMS
- Developed Instagram filter Spark AR and JavaScript
- Maintain website OctoberCMS, HTML, JavaScript, css and bootstrap
- Developed website Wordpress
- Developed EDM HTML/CSS
- Developed Interactive Camera Unity C#, API & JSON
- Research and development Environmental Soap Machine - Unity C#

## **Education History**

Bachelor of Arts and Science in New Media

Sep 2018 - Jun 2021

#### City University of Hong Kong

- Creative coding p5js, Processing and Arduino
- Game Develop Unity C#, C++
- Multimedia field

Higher Diploma in Multimedia

Sep 2016 - Jun 2018

Programme

#### Institute of Vocational Education

- Multimedia field
- Game Develop Unity C#